good morning
Good morning, sir.
Good morning.
What is it?
You had Mr. Yamamoto at an event in Hiroshima at the end of last year.
How was it? It was in my hometown.
It was a dream come true for me.
My father and mother came too.
They were so happy.
Of course, I had my favorites.
I guessed all of them.
I'm a DD, so...
I hope to work with the Carp in Hiroshima again, because I'm a DD.
I hope to work with the Carp in Hiroshima again.
To Mr. Yamamoto
Yes, what is it? You know him?
I don't know.
The Hiroshima Carp has officially asked me to work for them.
What?
It's an offer. - I don't know! I don't know! You mean you sing?
What do you mean?
I don't know.
I don't know if it's great or not.
Congratulations! Explain it to me.
"Curve, curve, curve" they play at every stadium.
I think everyone can sing it in Hiroshima Hiroshima
I can sing it.
We used to have a relay of celebrities who would sing it.
Jiro-san, Yongsun-san, Jiro-san, and others with connections to Hiroshima would relay the song.
It's going to skyrocket!
Every time, every time, every match.
I was told I could be a part of it.
I've been dreaming about it for a long time.
That's amazing!
Congratulations!
I've got to go do karaoke. I've got to do karaoke.
Teach me how to sing.
Please give me singing lessons.
How do you know so much?
The next time we shoot, we'll be in the masses.
Oh, my God!
I'll sing a lot every day.
You're really waving your hands!
I'm so happy!
What should I do, Mom?
Can I tell my family?
Oh, no.
No?
Yes, ma'am.
When will you tell them it's a bad idea?
Your father, your mother...
And the relatives.
I'll call all my friends.
I'll call all my friends. I'll call them all!
Come to Hiroshima with me!
I want to go! I wanna go! I want to go!
I'm going to the boat race with a musician.
That's great! Congratulations!
Congratulations! I'm so excited!
That's great!
Thank you very much.
I'll do my best!
That's great.
Good morning.
Today is the day of the shoot!
Yes, it is. Today is the day of the photo shoot for the Soleke Carp Celebrity Carp Fan Relay!
I'm so nervous.
I've got my Carp bag with me today.
I'm so happy to be allowed to be in such a wonderful thing.
I'm going to do my best as me!
Please watch over me!
Well, I'm off! I'll do my best!
Response to the corner
Waving to the audience
I'm allowed to take pictures of that kind of thing.
Shouting to the person in front of you
Or the part where you burst out with joy.
It's a little bit of a balance.
I'd like to get it.
Curve Curve Curve
Hiroshima Hiroshima Curve
Thank you very much.
Curve, Curve, Curve
Hiroshima Hiroshima Carp
Here we go!
Wow!
Oh! Yay!
Yes, thank you very much.
Now, when it's your turn, please come to the end of the line.
Yes, sir.
Carp Carp Carp Hiroshima Hiroshima Hiroshima Carp This is my own slidy.
I'll practice.
This is No. 1, and I've written about it before, but this is Slidey. I will practice.
This is No. 1.
I've written this before.
But you can do it, right?
It's okay. It's the end.
I felt it. I felt it after it was over.
But it was the first time for me to record something like this.
I was a little nervous.
It's a very strange feeling to think that I'm in the video that I've been watching until now.
It's a very strange feeling.
I'm looking forward to the completion of the project.
Today, I had Anne Yamamoto shoot a straight carp video for me.
The video has been deleted!
Wow!
That was fast!
I'm so nervous!
But I'm already too nervous.
I just really need to watch it.
Okay.
It's just us.
You want to see it in one shot?
Nervous?
Oh, my God!
It's starting!
Wait a minute.
Oh, my God! Oh, my God! Oh, is that it? Oh, it's started.
Oh, my gosh.
That's great.
Oh, my God.
Cute little Keys' chest twists and turns as he fights his way through this moment today.
I want to be far away!
Far away to the east
Let's stay parallel
Let's get up!
Carp, Carp, Carp Cure, that's great.
Thank you. The hair color is totally different.
Totally different.
Amazing!
Thank you very much.
Shaaaaa!
But because your voice sounded gruff.
Shhh!
Shaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaah!
I took various shaars.
This will be played at Matsuda Stadium for a year.
I'm so happy.
It was gorgeous, wasn't it?
Hey.
There are women.
It's great that you have a master, isn't it?
I haven't told my family or anyone yet.
What?
You haven't?
I haven't told anyone, so only the members know.
What are you going to do?
What are you going to do with your family? They won't be mad at you, Dad.
I wonder if they'll notice someday.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no. We have to invite them.
So, this is our next mission.
What?
Let's go see if this is the video that's being broadcast to Matsuda Stadium.
What? Yeah! Wait, wait, wait. Let's go see if we can get a visual on this going to Matsuda Studios. - Oh, no. - Audition? Audition for what? When are you going? When are you going?
Sunday of your ambition.
Soon!
Sunday of Ambition.
Sunday of ambition.
How many days?
I'm seven.
Seven.
Seven... seven... seven...
Is it open?
I'm open.
I'm off 7, and I'm thinking, "Yay.
You're coming with me.
I want to go, I want to go, I want to go.
I want to go to Hiroshima and see who's there.
See you all in Hiroshima!
I don't know why we've been here since the announcement.
I don't understand.
Why don't you go?
If the other members were here, there would be too many of us.
They're not here now.
What's the third one? Sanfrecce.
I like Sanfrecce already.
Wait a minute.
You're waking him up.
Wait a minute, Dad.
Dad, what are you doing?
Watching Sanfrecce.
Watching Sanfrecce. Where's Mom? Where's Mom?
Where's Mom?
Mom and Dad, come here for a moment.
Let me see your face.
Dad, how are you?
Yes, cut and see.
Yes, cut and see... Yes, I'm here, Katoh. Yay.
Oh, it's Minjin.
Hi, Mom. Is Mommy home?
Yes, I'm here.
Utsushi will get mad at me.
No, I'm fine with Utsushi.
No, no, no. Utsushi's fine.
Bye.
Oh, my gosh, this time,
Soreyuke Carp?
Oh.
You know, the famous relay of the "Soreyuke Carp"?
We were chosen for that!
Ume-chan, wow ... - I don't know why they changed the filter, but don't try to leak it, I'm going to see Hiroshima on April 7.
Can you come on April 7th?
Dad.
I'll be there.
Yes, sir.
Yes, I mean it.
He's cute.
That's great.
Bye-bye.
Congratulations.
Don't say it.
Don't say it. Bye-bye.
You look happy.
I snapped it off.
You look so happy.
She looked so happy.
Thank you very much.
The next mission.
I'm so happy. First of all, I'm so happy I get to go to Hiroshima.
I'm also happy to go to Matsuda Stadium
I've never been to Matsuda Stadium before.
I wish I could go there.
I hope that the three of us will be able to say that we arrived in Hiroshima
I hope we'll be able to say that we arrived in Hiroshima!
Will this be a movie?
Yes, from the announcement to the filming.
I'll ask you to do it.
So we'll make another one, of course.
Then we'll do it.
I'm flying.
This one.
Shall I do it already?
It's funny, if it wasn't for me.
You're talking more than you used to.
Okay, here we go!
So, I'm here at Slothman's...
Thank you very much.
Thank you very much!
How do you like it?
That's right.
He couldn't come today, so...
We're going to have fun today, just the two of us.
Yay! It's the first time I've been here.
I'm so glad.
It's my first time!
I'm so happy.
Isn't it bad?
It's supposed to rain today.
Oh, yeah.
It turned out to be a beautiful sunny day.
It's nice and sunny.
Now that the weather's better, I think we can win today.
I'm going to enjoy myself.
Anna is looking forward to it.
I'll do my best.
I was just having dinner.
Hitomi, who's here?
Anna's father is here!
Ahahahahaha!
Dad!
Oh my God, there's too many people in a row!
I'm so sorry, but I'm going to have a lot of fun with you today when I see the video of that...
Here it is, here it is, here it is, here it is!
We were together... and your father... your father... went away...
Yes, Dad? Dad's gone!
That's great!
That's great. Anchan, you're up.
I'll be right beside you.
I'm so nervous.
Which one? An-chan!
Oh, here it comes!
I got Khan-An-chan! I got Khan-An-chan! I got Khan-An-chan!
Ah, here it comes!
is coming!
a kaan a kaan a kaan
It's Shah, the first one!
It flowed!
It's done!
I'm so happy!
I'm so excited!
Oh my God!
Yaay, that's the only word that comes to mind.
I'm so happy!
I'm so happy to be watched over by so many people. I'm so happy, though I can't find any words but "Oh my God".
I'm so happy to be watched over by so many people.
Thank you so much. Thank you so much.
You're amazing.
Thank you so much. I'm so happy. You should all come and see it.
Come on, they're coming. It's going to flow.
It flows. It flows that way.
Wow, the wind. The wind. It's going to fly that way. Wind.
Here it comes. This is the second short version today.
Here it comes.
Ah! It's on! It's on!
Well, it's like that...
It's on!
It's big!
So much! Deep, deep Hiroshima herb!
Yay!
Yeah!
Yeah! Yea ... That's my friend's kid, just like Miyajima-san can sing!
To your place
What the heck!
So cute!
That's all
Yeah!